myebook.com 2018-12-19

# Myebook - get it out there!

  1. MyeBook Global Limited also known as Myebook and MyeBook,(sometimes abbreviated as Mye) of 24 Deansgate, Blackpool, Lancashire, FY1 1BN, UK and each of the companies in the MyeBook Group ("MyeBook") believes strongly in protecting your privacy and MyeBook complies with the Data Protection Act 1988. When you provide and MyeBook collects your personal information when you use the Site, MyeBook will use best endeavours only to use it or disclose it in the manner stated below and in accordance with current legislation and in line so as to meet current internet best practices. By using the Site you agree that MyeBook may do so.
  2. MyeBook will not disclose your personal details to other users except in accordance with this Privacy Policy.
  3. MyeBook reserves the right to send all registrants of our services e-mail communications from time to time regarding updates and changes to the services, new links to the Site and any technical, administrative or legal notices important to the Site and the services that MyeBook considers essential. You are not able to unsubscribe from these notices.
  4. MyeBook are the sole owners of the information collected on the Site. MyeBook will not sell, rent or otherwise disclose your personal information to any third party, without your consent, except in the following circumstances: 
    1. MyeBook does share non-personal, non-individual information in aggregate form with third parties for business purposes, for example with advertisers on the Site or we may tell our business partners the number of customers in certain demographic groups who use certain services. However, this does not involve disclosing any personal information which can identify any individual client in any way.
    2. MyeBook will disclose your personal information to any appropriate investigative third party if MyeBook believes that you are involved in any illegal or harmful conduct or if MyeBook is required to do so by law or MyeBook believes that such action is necessary to: 
      1. comply with the law or with legal process;
      2. protect and defend MyeBook's rights and property or that of other users;
      3. prevent fraud;
      4. protect against abuse, misuse or unauthorized use of the Site; or
      5. protect the personal safety or property of other users or the public (eg. if you provide false or deceptive information about yourself or attempt to pose as someone else, MyeBook will disclose such information about you as it has to assist any type of investigation into your actions).
    3. MyeBook may employ other companies to provide services for us. These companies have access to the personal information needed to perform their functions and not for any other purposes.
    4. MyeBook may transfer its user database, including personal information contained therein, to another company in the MyeBook Group or to a third party who acquires all or substantially all of the assets or stock in our company or the Site service whether by merger, acquisition, reorganisation or otherwise.
  5. The Site may contain links to other websites. Please note that MyeBook is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other websites and advise you to read the privacy statements of each website you visit which collects personal information.
  6. The "MyeBook Group" means any company which is a parent or holding company and any company which is a subsidiary or affiliate company of MyeBook Global Limited. 

A cookie is an alphanumeric identifier which MyeBook transfers to your hard drive through your web browser when you visit the Site. It enables MyeBook's own system to recognise you when you visit the Site again and improve our service to you. Cookies may also be used to compile aggregate information about areas of the Site that are visited most frequently. This traffic information can be used to enhance the content of the Site and make your use of it easier. MyeBook does not track which pages you looked at while visiting the Site. If you wish to reject our cookie, you can configure your browser to do so.
